<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>VittSeva</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on VittSeva</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 02:30:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Market Insights: Navigating the Evolving Landscape of Mutual Funds</title>
      <link>/blog/2025/09/16/2025-09-16-market-insights-navigating-the-evolving-landscape-of-mutual-/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 02:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/blog/2025/09/16/2025-09-16-market-insights-navigating-the-evolving-landscape-of-mutual-/</guid>
      <description>Explore the latest trends and regulatory changes in the mutual fund market that could impact your investments.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understanding Gold ETFs and Mutual Funds: Where Your Money Really Goes</title>
      <link>/blog/2025/09/16/2025-09-16-understanding-gold-etfs-and-mutual-funds-where-your-money-re/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 02:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/blog/2025/09/16/2025-09-16-understanding-gold-etfs-and-mutual-funds-where-your-money-re/</guid>
      <description>Explore the investment landscape of Gold ETFs and mutual funds to understand where your money is really going.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Market Dynamics Post-GST Reforms: What Investors Should Know</title>
      <link>/blog/2025/09/08/2025-09-08-market-dynamics-post-gst-reforms-what-investors-should-know/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 06:05:28 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>/blog/2025/09/08/2025-09-08-market-dynamics-post-gst-reforms-what-investors-should-know/</guid>
      <description>Explore how the recent GST reforms are reshaping market dynamics and investment strategies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Navigating the New GST Landscape: What It Means for Your Wallet</title>
      <link>/blog/2025/09/08/2025-09-08-navigating-the-new-gst-landscape-what-it-means-for-your-wall/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 06:05:28 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>/blog/2025/09/08/2025-09-08-navigating-the-new-gst-landscape-what-it-means-for-your-wall/</guid>
      <description>Explore the recent GST reforms in India and how they impact consumers and investors alike.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Market Insights: The Rise of Income Plus Arbitrage Funds</title>
      <link>/blog/2025/08/30/2025-08-30-market-insights-the-rise-of-income-plus-arbitrage-funds/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 06:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>/blog/2025/08/30/2025-08-30-market-insights-the-rise-of-income-plus-arbitrage-funds/</guid>
      <description>Discover the emerging trend of Income Plus Arbitrage Funds and their potential impact on investment strategies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Navigating Retirement: Is 3.5% the New Safe Withdrawal Rate?</title>
      <link>/blog/2025/08/30/2025-08-30-navigating-retirement-is-3-5-the-new-safe-withdrawal-rate/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 06:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>/blog/2025/08/30/2025-08-30-navigating-retirement-is-3-5-the-new-safe-withdrawal-rate/</guid>
      <description>Explore the evolving landscape of safe withdrawal rates for retirement and why 3.5% may be the new standard.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Finding Balance in the Pursuit of Financial Freedom</title>
      <link>/blog/2025/08/14/2025-08-14-finding-balance-in-the-pursuit-of-financial-freedom/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 11:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>/blog/2025/08/14/2025-08-14-finding-balance-in-the-pursuit-of-financial-freedom/</guid>
      <description>Explore the journey towards financial freedom without sacrificing your happiness.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Navigating the New Landscape of Investment Vehicles</title>
      <link>/blog/2025/08/14/2025-08-14-navigating-the-new-landscape-of-investment-vehicles/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 11:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>/blog/2025/08/14/2025-08-14-navigating-the-new-landscape-of-investment-vehicles/</guid>
      <description>Explore the emerging investment vehicles reshaping the financial landscape.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revisiting Stock Classifications: The Case for Expanding Large and Midcap Categories</title>
      <link>/blog/2025/07/29/2025-07-29-revisiting-stock-classifications-the-case-for-expanding-larg/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 02:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>/blog/2025/07/29/2025-07-29-revisiting-stock-classifications-the-case-for-expanding-larg/</guid>
      <description>Explore the implications of redefining stock classifications for investors and the market.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smart Strategies for Your Retirement Corpus: Making Rs 50 Lakh Work for You</title>
      <link>/blog/2025/07/29/2025-07-29-smart-strategies-for-your-retirement-corpus-making-rs-50-lak/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 02:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>/blog/2025/07/29/2025-07-29-smart-strategies-for-your-retirement-corpus-making-rs-50-lak/</guid>
      <description>Explore effective strategies for retirees to manage a Rs 50 lakh corpus for sustainable income.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Market Insights: The Rise of AI in Finance and Investment Strategies</title>
      <link>/blog/2025/07/14/2025-07-14-market-insights-the-rise-of-ai-in-finance-and-investment-str/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 10:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>/blog/2025/07/14/2025-07-14-market-insights-the-rise-of-ai-in-finance-and-investment-str/</guid>
      <description>Explore how AI is transforming finance and what it means for investors and markets.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Navigating the Trap of Illiquid Wealth: What You Need to Know</title>
      <link>/blog/2025/07/14/2025-07-14-navigating-the-trap-of-illiquid-wealth-what-you-need-to-know/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 10:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>/blog/2025/07/14/2025-07-14-navigating-the-trap-of-illiquid-wealth-what-you-need-to-know/</guid>
      <description>Discover how to avoid the pitfalls of illiquid investments and plan for a secure financial future.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Importance of insurance</title>
      <link>/blog/2023/08/01/importance-of-insurance/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 21:29:20 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>/blog/2023/08/01/importance-of-insurance/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-importance-of-insurance-a-must-have-for-every-individual&#34;&gt;The Importance of Insurance: A Must-Have for Every Individual&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Insurance is a crucial aspect of financial planning that provides protection and peace of mind to individuals and their families. In India, where uncertainty is a part of life, having comprehensive insurance coverage is essential. This blog post highlights why everyone should have insurance and provides a checklist of key information required to opt for life and medical insurances in India.&#xA;Why Everyone Should Have Insurance:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About Us</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Vitt Seva (वित्त सेवा), A financial services firm to make finance and related services simple, personal &amp;amp; optimal for individuals and businesses. Vitt (वित्त) means &amp;ldquo;Finance&amp;rdquo; and Seva (सेवा) means &amp;ldquo;Service&amp;rdquo; in Hindi. We chose this simple name to reflect our commitment to make  Financial decisions easy and optimum for our customers with our multi-brand - multi options services.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Our experienced &amp;amp; versatile teams&amp;rsquo; are deeply committed to providing highly personalised and optimised solutions as per the needs and budgets of each individual, group, and business. Right from protection to prosperity, we provide a wide range of options for most financial needs. Our advice is customised according to the needs and situation to offer the most optimum solutions.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accounting and Tax</title>
      <link>/service/accounting-tax/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/service/accounting-tax/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;streamlined-finances-optimized-returns&#34;&gt;Streamlined Finances, Optimized Returns&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Accounting and tax filing services are critical for both individuals and businesses to achieve financial stability and compliance. We offer comprehensive solutions for both, ranging from bookkeeping and tax planning to the preparation and filing of taxes. For individuals, we provide personalized services to help manage their finances and minimize their tax liability.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For businesses, we offer customized solutions to ensure accurate financial reporting and compliance with tax laws. With our team of experienced professionals, you can trust us to provide effective and efficient services.&#xA;Our aim is to serve you and achieve your financial objectives by providing reliable &amp;amp; quality accounting and tax filing services.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Business Banking</title>
      <link>/service/business-banking/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/service/business-banking/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;tailored-solutions-for-business-growth&#34;&gt;Tailored Solutions for Business Growth&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A start-up, an One Person Company, or an established high-revenue company; banking needs are different at different stages of the business.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We bring to you the right options as per your business needs for banking and invoicing, payment collection and payment settlements, payment instruments, and expense tracking for your employees.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;All these and much more through a completely online process to reduce your workload and manage very efficiently all your funds, finances, expenses, collections, taxes &amp;amp; tracking all of these.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Claim Settlement</title>
      <link>/service/claim-settlement/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/service/claim-settlement/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;efficient-solutions-for-fair-compensation&#34;&gt;Efficient Solutions for Fair Compensation&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Bringing your money back&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Yes! We help policyholders, shareholders, or customers with financial products in resolving the grievance of all verticals i.e. Life, Health and General Insurance, shareholding, Mutual funds, and many more.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A smooth and effortless claim redressal process is what we offer.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Our endeavor is to reach out to every customer to provide an efficient resolution to get the funds they deserve.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We bring customized service to nagging problems of Lost / Forgotten / Blocked investments in financial instruments such as Shares/ Mutual funds / Provident Funds / Insurance / Postal savings / Bank accounts etc.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/contact/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;we-are-here-to-help-you&#34;&gt;We are here to help you&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Are you curious about our offerings? Please use the form below to schedule a free consultation with us.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Please choose all the applicable services and share details about your requirement to help us serve you best.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAQ</title>
      <link>/faq/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/faq/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Pellentesque habitant morbi tristique senectus et netus et malesuada fames ac turpis egestas. Vestibulum tortor quam, feugiat vitae, ultricies eget, tempor sit amet, ante. Donec eu libero sit amet quam egestas semper. Aenean ultricies mi vitae est. Mauris placerat eleifend leo.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;1-what-to-do-if-i-have-still-not-received-the-order&#34;&gt;1. WHAT TO DO IF I HAVE STILL NOT RECEIVED THE ORDER?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Pellentesque habitant morbi tristique senectus et netus et malesuada fames ac turpis egestas. Vestibulum tortor quam, feugiat vitae, ultricies eget, tempor sit amet, ante. Donec eu libero sit amet quam egestas semper. Aenean ultricies mi vitae est. Mauris placerat eleifend leo.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Funding and Finance</title>
      <link>/service/funding-finance/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/service/funding-finance/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;fueling-ambitions-enabling-success&#34;&gt;Fueling Ambitions, Enabling Success&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Thinking of starting up or running a business, funding, and managing finances are crucial needs and can be a challenge at any point in time in the business.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We offer very selective and carefully associated experts who can make and manage these requirements and make your business experiences better to focus on your core strengths.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Our team will not only support fundraising; we may provide overall financial planning for your business.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Insurance</title>
      <link>/service/insurance/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/service/insurance/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;protection-made-personal&#34;&gt;Protection Made Personal&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The start of financial planning and a critical option to safeguard your hard-earned funds and peace of mind; in difficult times of life.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A strength to face the majority of challenges in one&amp;rsquo;s life that needs detailed planning, careful selection of options, and support from a trusted advisor.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;With us, unbiased advice, multiple options of the majority of insurers of all kinds of insurance, and much more are just a call away.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Investments</title>
      <link>/service/investment/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/service/investment/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;building-wealth-maximizing-potential&#34;&gt;Building Wealth, Maximizing Potential&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The next best thing is an investment if you have protected yourself with insurance options. With a gamut of variety of options suitable for all ages and financial statuses, one always needs experts to advise to decide on the most suitable investment options.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We offer the majority of moderate-risk options which are required for most of us and make them easy to understand for your needs.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Loans</title>
      <link>/service/loan/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/service/loan/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;unlocking-opportunities-empowering-growth&#34;&gt;Unlocking Opportunities, Empowering Growth&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Right from your small personal needs of quick money to large sums of the amount which will bring your dreams to true; we provide our expertise &amp;amp; network of lenders to get you the loans that are hassle-free, most cost-effective, and through a single advisor to avoid tiring efforts to deal with multiple agents or lenders.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;With us, your perception of the loan process will change and your experience will be much better than traditional agent services.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NRI Service</title>
      <link>/service/nri-service/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/service/nri-service/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We offer comprehensive NRI services to help Non-Resident&#xA;Indians (NRIs) manage their finances and investments in India. Our services include portfolio management, investment advisory, wealth management, and tax planning. We understand the unique financial needs of NRIs and offer customized solutions that suit their individual requirements.&#xA;Our team of experts is well-versed in the regulatory framework for NRIs and provides professional advice to help our clients make informed investment decisions. With our expertise and reliable services, NRIs can rest assured that their finances are in safe hands, even while they are residing abroad.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Service</title>
      <link>/services/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/services/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div id=&#34;vsat&#34; class=&#34;anchor&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;accounting-and-tax-filing&#34;&gt;Accounting and Tax Filing&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;streamlined-finances-optimized-returns&#34;&gt;Streamlined Finances, Optimized Returns&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Accounting and tax filing services&lt;/strong&gt; are critical for both individuals and businesses to achieve &lt;strong&gt;financial stability and compliance&lt;/strong&gt;. We offer &lt;strong&gt;comprehensive solutions&lt;/strong&gt;, ranging from &lt;strong&gt;bookkeeping and tax planning to tax preparation and filing&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For individuals, we provide &lt;strong&gt;personalized services&lt;/strong&gt; to help &lt;strong&gt;manage finances&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;minimize tax liability&lt;/strong&gt;. For businesses, we offer &lt;strong&gt;customized solutions&lt;/strong&gt; to ensure &lt;strong&gt;accurate financial reporting and compliance&lt;/strong&gt; with tax laws.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Work with us</title>
      <link>/work-with-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/work-with-us/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;internship-opportunity&#34;&gt;Internship Opportunity&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Vitt Seva, an emerging Financial Advisory Services firm, is seeking a talented Content Developer for its website.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;responsibilities&#34;&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The primary focus of this role is to refine existing content and prepare it for publication on our website.&#xA;The content will revolve around the services and products offered in Insurance, Investment, Loans, Funding, Claims Settlements, Real Estate, and Industry &amp;amp; Career updates.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;qualifications&#34;&gt;Qualifications:&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Applicants must possess:&#xA;A foundational understanding of Financial Services or a strong willingness to learn about the industry.&#xA;(Experience in similar content development is preferred but not mandatory.)&#xA;Excellent English writing skills.&#xA;Comfort with remote work.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
